(Sheldon:)...when I walked up to the podium
and looked out at the crowd.
(Sheldon:)There must have been
thousands of people.
(Sheldon:)My heart started pounding
in my chest.
(Sheldon:)I began to hyperventilate.
(Sheldon:)My vision became blurry,
and before I knew it--
(Sheldon:)Oh, dear.
(Penny:)-Oh, my God.
LEONARD: Sheldon?
(Leonard:)-Sheldon, are you okay?
-Don't trample me.
SHELDON: Come on, Mother, you know
why I can't accept the award.
(Sheldon:)With all due respect,
I don't think praying will help.
(Sheldon:)No, I have not heard the song
"Jesus, Take the Wheel."
(Sheldon:)No, no, no.
You don't need to start singing it.
Yes, I'll buy it on "the iTunes,"
Mother.
(Sheldon:)Goodbye, Mother.
(Sheldon:)Hello.
-Sit down. We wanna talk to you.
-Am I in trouble?
(Sheldon:)Did my mother call you?
(Penny:)Just sit.